Guide to the Stanford University Architectural Collection SC1043
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Architectural drawings
  - Stanford Village, circa 1948 (Box A1)
    Description: Stanford Village - a Stanford University residence area--[Plot map]
  - Stern Research Lab (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Stern Research Lab for Stanford Medical School, San Francisco
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, 1961 Jun 12 (Box A1)
    Architect: Luckman Associates
    Description: Test Lab (SLAC?)
    Format: photograph of sketches
  - [earthquake analysis] (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: 1906 earthquake analysis
  - [housing density], 1960 (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Residential density comparison between UC and Stanford
    Format: chart
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Proposed pedestrian paths for Serra Street vicinity of the Oval and Main Quad
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Proposed connecting path - bookstore/Meyer Library
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Study for location of pedestrian and bicycle circulation
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Existing and proposed pedestrian and bicycle routes, Mayfield to Escondido, Lasuen to Lomita
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Development scheme for mall, Galvez Street (Serra to Campus Drive)
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Proposed extension of Serra (between Galvez Street and Lasuen Mall)
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Proposed extension of Serra Street sidewalk between Lomita Mall and Via Palou
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Location study of bicycle path to serve fraternity cluster #2
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Proposed traffic lane and pedestrian crosswalk striping Galvez and Serra Streets
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Proposed extension of Serra Street sidewalk between Galvez Street and Arguello Way
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Proposed extension of Serra Street sidewalk between Campus Drive and Arguello Way
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Lasuen pedestrian and bicycle pathway route
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Study of bicycle path for divided road (Serra Street extended)
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Bicycle paths
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Bicycle path between El Camino and Campus Drive near Galvez Street
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Plan for bicycle paths - El Camino to Galvez at Campus Drive; Arboretum Road to Lasuen at Memorial Way
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Pedestrian and bicycle pathways
  - Student health center (Box map case)
    Description: Pedestrian and bike path to student health center
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Bicyle-pedestrian path to service College Terrace and married student housing
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Mayfield sidewalk
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Path study Frenchman’s Hill
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Stanford Avenue path
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Location schematic path and lights - westerly side Mayfield Avenue
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Possible improvements to Foothill Road to provide pedestrian paths--[original list says “Where kept?”]
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Construction plan - details - specifications for construction of eight foot wide path along Searvsville Road from Los Arboles Avenue to Willow Road at bridge
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Proposed bicycle routes - a circulation and parking program for Stanford University
  - Paths/Roads (Box map case)
    Description: Study of pedestrian circulation
  - Library (1905), circa 1905 (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Elevations, floor plans, and cross section of the 1905 Library (destroyed by the 1906 earthquake)
  - Memorial Auditorium parking, 1969 Mar 13 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Proposed interim parking lot and outdoor lighting fixture installation, vic. of Memorial Auditorium
  - Oval, 1964 Sep 7 (Box map case Na19)
    Architect: Church, Thomas D.
    Description: Oval - Stanford University - Master Plan Study; shows landscaping and projected buildings [quad number is a guess]
    Format: diazo print with colored pencil details
  - Ronald Reagan Library, May-86 (Box map case Nd3)
    Description: Topographic Survey Ronald Reagan Library Site (2 copies of site topo; 2 copies of building footprints superimposed on topo)
    Format: diazo prints (?)
  - Ronald Reagan Presidential Library, 1986 Apr 7 (Box map case Nd3)
    Architect: Stubbins Associates Inc.
    Description: The Ronald Reagan Presidential Library - location plan, site plan, ground floor, second floor, basements, elevations, sections
    Format: blueprints, stapled together
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 1986 Aug 1 (Box map case Nd3)
    Description: The Ronald Reagan Presidential Library - grading plan, site sections, ground floor, second floor, basements
  - Stanford residence, Sacramento, 1986 (Box map case Nd5)
    Architect: Historic American Buildings Survey
    Description: Leland Stanford House, sheets 2-9 (of 9): site plan, floor plans, north elevation, west elevation, transverse section A-A; these are marked “unedited by HABS”
    Format: paper prints
  - Memorial Court, unknown (Box map case Na6-7)
    Description: Memorial Court [mostly detailing decorative pavement, with some indication of lawn and flowers]
    Format: pencil on paper, with glued on labels
  - Memorial Court, 1981 May 11 (Box map case Na6-7)
    Description: Memorial Court Study
    Format: pen on yellow tracing paper; blueprint copy with color additions
  - Memorial Court, unknown (Box map case Na6-7)
    Description: Memorial Court Existing
  - Stanford Residence (Palo Alto), undated (Box map case Nd5)
    Architect: Bugbee, S. C. and Sons
    Description: Basement Plan. Residence Hon. Leland Stanford
    Format: ink on linen, encapsulated
  - Library Quad, circa 1930 (Box SAL 290)
    Description: Library Quad proposals, ca. 1930--[rolled in tube and stored at SAL]
  - Stanford Residence (Palo Alto), undated (Box map case Nd5)
    Format: copy on vellum (done 1/30/98 at request of Laura Jones, planning office)
  - Stanford Convalescent Home, undated (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Proposed Layout Stanford Home for Convalescent Children Stanford Campus
  - Stanford residence, Sacramento (Box SAL)
    Description: Stanford Sacramento House, drawings --[rolled in tube and stored at SAL]
  - Hoover Library Group ? (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Untitled perspective sketch, possibly for proposed food research, war memorial, and Hoover Library Group as drawn up by Bakewell and Brown - see Oct. 14, 1930 plan
    Format: pencil on tissue; in mount and mylar envelope
  - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. Cleaveland Forbes, 1929 Feb 23 (Box map case Nd5)
    Architect: Carmack, Willa Cloys, landscape architect
    Description: Planting Plan Residence of Mr. and Mrs. Cleaveland Forbes, Atherton, Ca. with plant list
  - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. Cleaveland Forbes, 1929 Feb 9 (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Planting Plan for Drive and Forecourt, Mr. and Mrs. Cleaveland Forbes, Atherton, Ca. with plant list
  - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. Cleaveland Forbes, 1929 Feb 9 (Box map case Nd5)
    Architect: Leland and Haley, engineers
    Description: Arrangement of Heating Equipment. Residence for Mr. and Mrs. Cleaveland Forbes, Woodside, CA
  - G. S. Little House (Box C2)
    Description: Plot map for G. S. Little House, Scheme A (18th Street and New York Avenue)
  - Proposed new quad (Box B2)
    Architect: Bakewell and Brown (?)
    Description: No title - possibly proposed new Quad or Hoover buildings.--Received in the Stanford Collection May 14, 1941.
  - Football Bleachers, 13-Jul (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Addition to Football Bleachers, Athletic Field. Sheet No. 2 (elevations and details) and Sheet No. 1 (materials, instructions).
  - Quad, 1915 Apr 23 (Box A1)
    Description: Plan of Existing and Proposed Buildings Leland Stanford Jr. University
    Format: Color photograhic reproduction of os blueprint classed as Map 1100
  - Paths/Roads, 1994 (Box map case Nd5)
    Architect: Tom Richman and Associates
    Description: Palm Drive Reconstruction Project No. 9302
    # of Drawings: 45
  - Palo Alto Tree, 1920 (Box D1)
    Description: Plan showing proposed concrete curbing and leaf mould filling around Palo Alto redwood tree, Palo Alto, Calif. April 23, 1920
  - Camp Fremont ?? (Box Basement MC)
    Description: Drawings for horse shed, gun shed, and barracks (WW1?)
    Format: pencil and ink on tissue
  - Newark Storage Facility - Library portion, 2001 May 16 (Box map case Nd5)
    Architect: Ross Mc Donald Company Shelving Systems
    Description: Shelving layout for Stanford University Libraries Newark Storage Facility
    Format: photocopy on paper
  - Stanford Home for Convalescent Children (Box C2)
    Description: Perspective sketch for the Stanford Home for Convalescent Children donated by Mrs. Henry J. Crocker in memory of Kate Dillon McLoughlin. Pencil with watercolor
    Format: original pencil sketch with watercolor
  - Lane Medical Library, 1911 Jun 27 (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Foundation Plan. Medical Library for the Trustees of the Leland Stanford Junior University. S.E. Cor. Sacramento and Webster Sts., S.F. June 27, 1911
  - Stanford Convalescent Home for Children, 1923 (Box Basement MC)
    Description: Plot plan for Stanford Home for Convalescet [sic] Children, May 9, 1923
  - Stanford Convalescent Home for Children, 1927 (Box Basement MC)
    Description: Proposed layout for Stanford Home for Convalescent Children, Oct. 21, 1927
  - Stanford Convalescent Home for Children, 1927 (Box Basement MC)
    Artist: Blume and Makle
    Description: Stanford Convalescent Home lease; Area 26.5 acres; July 1932. Surveyed and drawn by Blume and Makle
  - Stanford Residence (Palo Alto), 1890 (Box map case Nd5)
    Architect: Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge
    Description: Plan showing position of rainwater and sewer pipes surrounding the house. ca. 1890
  - Miscellaneous buildings, 1941-42 (Box Basement MC)
    Artist: H. C. Scherer
    Description: [Plant ]maintenance areas - drawings for campus locations showing plant masses [not individual plants/trees]
  - Plan and Elevation, Lodge, cabin
  - Kitchen, Dining, Living Rm, Sash, Sil
  - Dining Room Bldg, Chimney
  - Toilet and Wash House Bldg
  - Fishing Lodge on the Rapid Anne & Wilson Rivers, 1929
- Cantor Arts Center design records, 1938-2000; Accession ARCH-2013-029
  - Architectural archives project
    Papers relating to the rebuilding after the 1989 earthquake. Arranged according to project phases. See index in Box 1, Folder 1.
    - Architectural Archives Project Index, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Report on Structural Investigation of First Floor Rotunda Area, 1978 Oct 31 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Construction of Stanford Museum, 1938-1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Unlabeled Photos, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Stanford University Museum of Art Feasibility Study, 1990 Nov 19 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Museum Historical Background, 1964-1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Renovations: Main Lobby, 1978-1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Earthquake Report Damage, 1989 Oct (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - SUMA - Schemes Rejected, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - SUMA Final Program Scheme - Plans, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Earthquake Damage Report, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Historical Museum Rebuilding Program, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Marble Accident, 1986-1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Damage and Repair, 1972-1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Floor Plans: Exhibition Space, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Floor Plans: Space Inventory, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Handicap Access (Arch. Access), 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Renovation: "Pre-89 Quake Estimates", 1989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - SUMA Rebuilding Project, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Stanford University Museum of Art - Space Program, 1994 Jan 14 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Stanford University Appeal to the Regional Director, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Memo, Request for Proposal, Portion of WTA/CMA proposal, Architect Reference Reports, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - SUMA Rebuild Stanford Approvals, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Program Requirements: Public, Galleries, Support Spaces, Administrative, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Space Data Sheets, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Senior Staff Review Set, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Schematic Design, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Statement of Qualifications, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Competition Submittal, April 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Proposal for the Stanford Museum Restoration and Expansion, April 1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Restoration and Expansion Written Proposal, April 1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Architect Selection, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Architect References, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Architect's Information, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Architect Questionaires and Slides, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Architectural Selection, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Manual for Materials and Finishes pt. 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Manual for Materials and Finishes pt. 2 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Manual for Materials and Finishes pt. 3, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Materials, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Skylight Covers, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Overhead Coiling Doors Request, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Request Submittals pt. 1 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Request Submittals pt. 2 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Field Observation, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Response to Requests, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Meeting Minutes pt. 1, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Rudolph and Sletten Hot List, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Meeting Minutes pt. 2, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Request Submittals, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Arata Isozaki & Associates, 34451 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - C. David Robinson Architects, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Building Plans, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - C. David Robinson and Architects, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Polshek and Partners Architects, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Rudolph and Sletten, Inc., 1995 October (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Oppenheim Lewis, Inc. Estimate of Construction Cost, Ausust 29, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Rudolph and Sletten 70% CD Estimate, 34941 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Polshek and Partners Architects Audiovisual, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Charles M. Salter Associates Audiovisual, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Polshek and Partners Associates Bid Procedures, January 1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Bid- Asbestos, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - SUMA-Schedule, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Polshek and Partners Contract, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Degenkolb, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Flack and Kultz Consulting Engineers, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - SWA Group, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - PHA Lighting, May 1994 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence-Laura Jones, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence-Sandro Amaglio, October 1995 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Museum Issues, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Historic Structure Report, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Other Consultants, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Site Clearance, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Parking, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Construction Management, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Polshek and Partners, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Other Consultants, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - D. D. Review, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Design and Program, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Meeting Minutes p. 1, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Meeting Minutes p. 2, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Basic Values, June 1994 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Testing, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Misc., 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - XRF Database (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Cost Renovation/Expansion, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 35a)
    - Cost Estimate, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - F.F.E Drafts, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Ground Breaking, 1995 October (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Asbestos, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Disaster/Recovery/Response, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Encina Rehab (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Brown Building, 1993-1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Building Problems, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - F.F.E. Tom, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Cantor Center- Building on the Past, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Cantor Center- Future Expense Consolidation, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Audio Visual (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - One Time Costs to Reopen, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Past and Present, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Essay on Cantor by Ryan Roth, 35108 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Casework (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Cantor Center- Punch List p.1, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Cantor Center- Punch List p. 2, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Cantor Center- Project Budget, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence- Maggie Burgett p. 1, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence- Maggie Burgett p. 2, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence- Maggie Burgett p. 3, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Stanford Museum Renovation/Expansion Schedule, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Gallery Punch List, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Meeting Minutes for Stanford Museum Renovation/Expansion, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - SMRE- Issues and Items, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Climate Control- SMRE, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence-Kathleen Baldwin, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence- Richard Koshelvk p. 1, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence- Richard Koshelvk p. 2, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence- Thomas Seligman, Michael Conroy, etc., 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence- Thomas Seligman p. 1, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence- Thomas Seligman p. 2, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence- Thomas Seligman p. 3, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - C. David Robinson Architects, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - SMRE Financial, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Polshek and Partners Architects, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Paint Analysis, 1996 Jun (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence-Misc, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Accesories for the Renovation of Cantor Center (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Rudolph and Sletten, Inc. Reports, Correspondence, etc, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Drawings/ Issues, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - SMRE-Bid Problem p. 1, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - SMRE- Bid Problem p. 2, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - SMRE- Bid Problem p. 3, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - SMRE- Bid Problem p. 4, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - SMRE- Bid Problem p. 5, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Architectural drawings
    - Isozaki, Arata, 1931-, presentation drawings, 1997; 2000.7.1:9 (Map-case Sf8)
    - James S. Polshek and Partners (U.S.A., 1980), presentation drawings (watercolor), 1997; 2000.8.1:6 (Item 7)
    - James S. Polshek and Partners (U.S.A., 1980), presentation drawings, 1997; 2000.9.1:22 (Map-case Sc18, Map-case Sd17, Map-case Sc20, Map-case Sc17, Map-case Sb20, Map-case Sc19, Map-case Sb19)
    - James S. Polshek and Partners (U.S.A., 1980), presentation photographs, 1997; 2000.10.1-5 (Map-case Sb10)
    - James S. Polshek and Partners (U.S.A., 1980), working sketches, 1998-1999; 2000.11.1-194
    - Turnbull, William, 1935-, presentation drawings, 1997; 2000.12.1-41 (Map-case Sd15, Map-case Sd18, Item 6)
    - Rudolph & Sletten, Project Construction Schedule, 1998-1999; 2000.13 (Map-case Sd17)
    - 8x10" copy negative "Map of lands situated in Santa Clara and San Mateo counties, The property of Leland Stanford, Surveyed at request of Ariel Lathrop 1883"
    - photocopies of Stanford University land maps (details of main quad and oval)
    - 4 sets of plans/blue prints (and some related documents) for Rodin Sculpture Garden by Mittelstadt, Robert, 1982-1985
    - 2 loose sheets and 2 sheets stapled together of plans for Rodin Sculpture Garden by Mittelstadt, Robert, 1982-85; 4 item(s)
    - plans for Rodin Sculpture Garden by Mittelstadt, Robert, 1982?
    - plans for Rodin Sculpture Garden's Gates of Hell support wall by Western Art Stone Co., 1984
    - matted plans of Museum's north wing (basement, 1st floor, 2nd floor)
    - Preliminary sketch for Frank Buck Gallery by Daily, Gardner A., 1966
    - 3 sets of blueprints/ plans for Museum's south rotunda gallery remodel by Raymond M. Rooker & Assoc., 1980
    - plan for Museum's painting storage proposed installation design by Kommer, Frank, 1983
    - plan of Museum's original footprint pre 1906 at 1":16' scale
    - matted plan for the Thomas Welton Stanford Art Gallery by Bakewell & Brown, 1916
    - loose copies of same plan as above for the Thomas Welton Stanford Art Gallery by Bakewell & Brown, 1916
    - plan for the Stanford Art Gallery by Lippold, Larry, 1989
    - plan for the Stanford Art Gallery by the Stanford Planning Office, 1952
- McMurtry Building for Art & Art History drawings, 1996-2015; Accession ARCH-2016-115
  - Art into Anatomy - draft feasibility report, 2003-06-18 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Art into Anatomy - draft feasibility report, 2003-06-18 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Move Plan, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - McMurtry, 2013-2015 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - McMurtry, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - New Art Building, 2008-2011 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Thomas Welton Stanford Art Gallery & Nathan Cummings art - planning study, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Thomas Welton Stanford Art Gallery & Nathan Cummings Art Building, 1996-08-23 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Thomas Welton Stanford Art Gallery & Nathan Cummings Art Building, Facilities Analysis and Space Planning Study, 1996-08-23 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Allsteel Stride packet, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - McMurtry Building Stanford University Giving opportunities, 2014-02 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Presentation space, seating space, 2014-02-2014-07 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Mc Murtry Proposed Ancillary Furniture and layouts presentation, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Stanford McMurtry Art History Building layouts, 2014-7 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University McMurtry Building Floor plans, 2013-02-2013-03 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Stanford University McMurtry Building Floor plans and draft working program, 2011-2014 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Ricardo Scofido contact Studio Profile, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Floor plans, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Stanford University McMurtry Building, 2011-11-17 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - McMurtry Building Stanford University Programming & Concept Design Report draft #1 Room Data Sheets, 2011-03-30 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - McMurtry Building Stanford University Programming & Concept Design Report draft #1 Room Data Sheets, 2011-03-30 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - McMurtry Building Stanford University Programming & Concept Design Report draft #2 incorporates comments received by Design Team as of April 22, 2011, 2011-04-27 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - McMurtry Building Stanford University Programming & Concept Design Report draft #2 incorporates comments received by Design Team as of April 22, 2011, 2011-04-27 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - McMurtry Building Stanford University Programming & Concept Design Report, 2011-06-09 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - McMurtry Building Stanford University Schematic Design, 2011-12-12 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - McMurtry Building Stanford University 50% Design Development, 2012-07-20 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - McMurtry Building Stanford University Design Development, 2012-09-21 (Box 5, Folder 3)